In this section, we will look into how we can climb up, climb down, climb to the left,
在这一部分，我们将研究如何向上爬，向下爬，向左爬，
climb to the right, climb up the ledge, climb down the ledge, enter and exit the climb state.
向右爬，爬上岩架，爬下岩架，进入和退出爬升状态。
We will begin with creating an NMInstance class in C++, then rebuild our existing animation
我们将从用C++创建一个NMInstance类开始，然后重新构建现有动画
blueprint.
蓝图。
Once we have all the state machines ready, we will go through the MixML animation pipeline
一旦我们准备好了所有的状态机，我们将通过MixML动画管道
and look at how we can use the MixML converter to help us retarget animation.
然后看看如何使用MixML转换器来帮助我们重定动画目标。
Then we will take care of the climb locomotion, along with the floor check for exiting the
然后我们将负责爬升运动，以及退出的地板检查。
climb state.
爬升状态。
We will also create another algorithm to help us detect the ledge and learn how to use control
我们还将创建另一个算法来帮助我们检测边缘并学习如何使用控制
rig to adjust the animation that we get from MixML.
装备以调整我们从MixML获得的动画。
Next, with everything we have learned, we will look into how we can use another algorithm
接下来，结合我们所学到的所有内容，我们将研究如何使用另一种算法
to help us to check whether or not we can climb down and use the same process to have
帮助我们检查我们是否可以爬下去，并使用相同的过程来
a working animation for climbing down.
向下爬的工作动画。
This is going to be a cool section with tons of new stuff for you to dive into.
这将是一个很酷的部分，有大量的新东西供你潜入其中。
When you are ready, let's get started.
当你准备好了，我们就开始吧。
[